穿这么帅要去哪里
Wow! You look nice. What's the occasion?
莫妮卡和我要庆祝相恋十个月
Monica and I are celebrating our ten-month anniversary,
我们在乔治法国餐厅订了位
we've got reservations at Ja George.
你们怎么订得到的
Wow! How'd you get in there?
打了几通电话  动用一些关系
Made a few calls, pulled some strings,
他们同意让我们十一点半进去
and they agreed to seat us at 11:30
而且都点鸡肉不吃甜点
if we both had the chicken and didn't get desert.
钱德勒
Hi Chandler!
凯特琳  新发型哦
Hey Caitlin! Somebody got a haircut.
我讨厌死了  活像八岁小男孩
Ugh, I hate it! I look like an 8-year-old boy.
如果真的是这样
Yeah, if that was true,
那以前上体育课会有趣许多
gym class would've been a lot more interesting.
正好二十七块
It's uh, 27 dollars even.
好  给你
Oh, okay.  Here you go.
阿鸡去哪里了
Hey, where's the chicken?
在后头  被阿鸭气跑了
Oh, he's in the back. The duck pissed him off,
阿鸭说先有蛋才有鸡
said that eggs came first.
谢了  下回见
Great. I'll see you later!
好  再见
Okay, bye!
你那样算是什么
What the hell was that?!
什么
What?
打情骂俏  你不是正要去
The flirting! Aren't you supposed to be going out with,
跟谁来着  跟我妹妹约会吗
I don't know hmm, let's say my sister?!
我没在打情骂俏啊
I was not flirting.
那根本就是打情骂俏
It was totally flirting.
新发型哦
"Somebody got a haircut "
首先  你模仿得很恐怖
Okay first of all, the impression, uncanny.
第二  那不是打情骂俏  只是两个人
And second, that was not flirting, that was just casual conversation
闲话家常而已
between two people. That is all.
才怪
Yeah, right.
你要看打情骂俏吗  我示范给你看
You wanna see flirting? I'll show you flirting.
不用了
I'm good.
我真替乔伊感到骄傲
I am so proud of Joey,
他竟然参演了《法律与秩序》
I can't believe he's going to be on Law & Order!
可是你不觉得叫《秩序与法律》比较对吗
I know. But don't you think that it should be called Order and Law?
不对  得先把人逮捕了才能审讯啊
No because first they arrest the guy and then they try him.
我对这点可是窝了一肚子意见
Don't get me started on that.
我没在打情骂俏
I was not flirting.
还在纪念日当天  你脸皮真厚
And on your anniversary, for shame!
怎么了
What's going on?
钱德勒跟外送辣妹打情骂俏
Chandler was hitting on the hot delivery girl!
我才没有  老天  闭嘴
I was not and oh God, shh!
有就是有
Well I'm sorry but you were! Okay?
而且就算有谁要跟她搭讪
And besides if anyone should be hitting on her
也应该是单身的男人
it's the guy who's single, the guy that who-
应该是有搞头的人嘛
who-who can do something about it.
看来有人喜欢披萨外送妹啊
Sounds like somebody wants to be Mr. Pizza Delivery Girl.
原来是这样  你喜欢凯特琳
Is that what this is about? You like Caitlin?
罗斯  我们分手都两年了
Ross! We broke up two years ago;
中间你还结过婚
you've been married since then.
我们各自约会应该没问题吧
I think it's okay that we see other people.
我那天在披萨店看到她
Well, I-I was watching her the other day at the pizza place.
她性感又风趣  还有小巧可爱的...
And she's just so sexy and funny and has the cutest little...
三围不用说
Okay, y'know what? We don't need her measurements.
三个都是意式腊肠披萨  罗斯
Okay pepperoni, pepperoni, pepperoni, okay Ross,
我知道她人美你又爱  但她是不是蠢了点
I know she's pretty and you love her, but is she stupid?!
她忘了我点的素食披萨
She forgot my vegetarian!
太完美了  她一定会再来送你的素食披萨
This is perfect! She'll have to come back here with your pizza,
到时我就展现出罗斯的魅力
and when she does, I'll turn on the Charm-O-Ross.
我真高兴你不吃肉
Oh I'm so glad you don't eat meat.
看吧  吃素对大家都好
See? Vegetarianism benefits everyone.
大家看是谁来了  还记得我奶奶吗
Hey everybody, look who's here! You remember my grandmother!
-非常之夜  -太酷了
- Big night! - This is so cool!
乔伊参演《法律与秩序》  你一定很骄傲吧
So, Joey on Law & Order, you must be very proud!
钱德勒  她完全听不懂英文
Chandler, she doesn't understand a word of English.
抱歉  我以为你是乔伊另一个奶奶
I'm sorry, I thought you were Joey's other grandmother.
我还猛说英文
I've done it again.
她是我的头号影迷
She's my biggest fan.
家族里只有她一个  自始至终都相信我
Yeah, she's the only one in the family who's always believed in me.
对  大明星
Si. Big star.
我的胖胖乔伊大明星
My big fat Joey star.
对  我出生时重十二公斤  所以...
Yeah, I uh weighted like 27 pounds when I was born so...
纪念日快乐
Hey! Happy Anniversary!
十个月纪念日快乐
Happy Anniversary, 10 months!
我刚才在淋浴的时候
So umm, when I was in the shower
想起我们在伦敦的第一晚
I was thinking about our first night in London...
乔伊的奶奶来了
Uhh, Joey's grandmother is right there.
会说英文的那个还是不会的
Is that the one that speaks English or the one that doesn't?
不会的那个
The one that doesn't.
那晚你给我的爱还真是火热
That was some hot love you gave me!
我去准备一下
I'm gonna go get ready.
不如戴我送你的耳环吧
Hey, why don't you wear those earrings I gave you?
好主意  我就是留到特别场合戴的
That's a great idea! I was saving them for something special.
好
Okay.
你得回家去
You have got to go home!
但是我喜欢这里啊
But I like it here!
你得回家拿我借你的耳环
You gotta go home and get the earrings that you borrowed from me okay?
钱德勒要我今晚戴那副耳环
Chandler wants me to wear them tonight.
好  应该是放在我皮包里
Okay, well I think that they're in my purse.
你去换衣服  我去找
Why don't you go get dressed and I'll look for them.
好
Great!
瑞秋  我要拿回我借你的耳环
Rach, hi, I need those earrings you borrowed.
好的  我马上拿来
Oh, umm, okay, yeah, I'll be, yeah I'll be right back.
菲比  你会说意大利语吗
Wow Pheebs, you speak Italian?
我猜是吧
I guess so.
来  谢谢你
Here you go. Thank you!
瑞秋  等等  另外一只呢
Wait, Rach! Where's the other one?
你两个都要吗
Oh what, you-you want both of them?
瑞秋·凯伦·格林  另一只耳环呢
Rachel Karen Green, where's the other earring?!
好啦  你先别生气  好像不见了
Okay, okay, okay, look, just don't freak out, but I kinda lost it.
还在公寓里  但一定不见了
I know it's in the apartment, but I definitely lost it.
那我要怎么跟莫妮卡说
Well, what am I going to tell Monica?
她今晚就要戴
She wants to wear them tonight!
叫她戴自己的耳环
Tell her to wear her own earrings.
这就是她的耳环
These are her earrings.
不  不  你把莫妮卡的耳环借我
Nooo! Nooooo! You lent me Monica's earrings?!
我不能借她的东西的
I'm not allowed to borrow her stuff!
为什么
Why not?
因为我都会弄丢
Because I lose her stuff!
看到那个盲人没
Okay, see that blind guy right there?
我等一下会痛打他一顿
I'm gonna bash his head in later.
我的戏就快到了  我的戏就快到了
Oh umm, my big scene is coming up. Big scene coming up.
若你说"吃葡萄不吐葡萄皮"
If you said, "Big lima bean, bubbling up."
她会不会比较懂
Would she understand the difference?
瑞秋  你在干嘛
Rach? What are you doing?
我不敢看  太恐怖了
I just can't watch. It's too scary!
现在是纸尿裤的广告
It's a diaper commercial.
你也知道我的  小孩啊  责任  吓死人
Oh yeah well, you know me, babies, responsibilities, ahhh!!!
披萨外送
Pizza delivery!
我来开  我来拿
I'll get it! I will get that!
一个素食披萨  十二块五
One uh, vegetarian pizza. That's $12.5.
对了  如果这会让你好过些
Oh. Uh, by the way, if it makes you feel any better.
我正好很喜欢八岁男孩
I happen to like 8-year-old boys.
什么
What?!
不是  我是说
No, I mean...
之前你说过  你的发型
your hair, before, your hair,
你说你的发型很像八岁男孩
you said you thought your hair looks like an 8-year-old's,
我说我很喜欢  你的发型
and I'm just saying I like it. The hair.
谢谢
Oh. Thanks.
我不是真的喜欢八岁男孩
You understand I don't actually like 8-year-old boys.
我在等你付钱
Y'know, all I'm looking for is the money.
这里  别再帮我们送披萨了
Here you go. Now stop bringing us pizzas you.
我会哭的
I'm gonna cry.
不客气
You're welcome.
你就是不想看我得手  对吧
You couldn't let me have her, could ya?!
什么
What?
我很喜欢这个女孩  你非得来凑热闹
This is a girl that I really like and you had to swoop in there!
怎么了
What's goin' on?
钱德勒冲着外送辣妹打情骂俏
Chandler was totally flirting with the hot delivery girl!
真是多谢你了
Thank you for that!
我没有打情骂俏
I was not flirting.
没关系  我不在意  无所谓
It's okay. I don't care. It's uh, it's fine.
-真的吗  -真的吗
- Really?! - Really?!
小事一件  我一直这样
It's no big deal, I do it all the time.
你一直都跟男人打情骂俏吗
So umm, you-you flirt with guys all the time?
是啊  那又不代表什么
Sure! It doesn't mean anything!
你不是也没别的意思吗
Just like I know it doesn't mean anything with you!
对  但是有很大区别  你比我迷人多了
Okay, but there is a big difference. You are a lot hotter than I am.
这是真的
True story!
钱德勒  你真的介意吗
Chandler, this actually bothers you?
对  我是介意  我想很多人都会介意
Yes, it does bother me! And I think it would bother a lot of people.
瑞秋  你和罗斯在一起时
Rachel, when you were going out with Ross,
他跟别的女人打情骂俏  你会不会介意
did it bother you when he flirted with other women?
不会  他跟别的女人上床我才会介意
Uhh, no, no, it bothered me when he slept with other women.
真是多谢了
And thank you, for that.
但其实我没啥好担心的
But y'know, I never really had anything to worry about.
罗斯从来就不太会打情骂俏
Ross was never very good at the flirting thing.
你在说什么啊
What? What-what, what are talking about?
对你不就很有效吗
It-it worked with you.
你说的真是对极了
Oh! Y'know what? You're right!
我们认识  你对我打情骂俏
We meet, you flirted and
九年后你终于追到我了
then bamn nine years later you had me!
好吧  就这么办
All right, all right. You-you-you know what I'm going to do?
我再点个披萨  等凯特琳来了后
I am going to order another pizza and when Caitlin gets here,
我就让你们见识一下  我有多会打情骂俏
you-you--I will show how well I flirt.
我还能要到她的电话号码
Yeah! I will, I will get her phone number!
不是披萨店的电话啦
And not the one on the menu!
我找到了
I found it!
谢天谢地  在哪里找到的
Ohh! Thank God! Where was it?
在你的梳妆台上
On your dresser.
那是本来就有的那一只
Okay that is the one we already have!
我的戏开始了  开始了
Okay, here's my big scene. My big scene's here!
天啊
Oh my God.
干嘛
What?
大家继续笑
Okay, everybody just keep smiling.
我奶奶发现一定会难过到死掉
It'll kill my grandmother if she finds out.
怎么了
Well, what is it?
我那一段被剪掉了
Oh, they cut me out of the show.
什么
What?!
你确定吗
Are you sure?
或许等一下才到你的戏份
Maybe your scene's coming up?
不太可能  看到那个装尸体的袋子没
Not likely. 'Cause you see that body bag right there
有啊
Yeah.
里头装的是我
I'm in it.
太糟糕了  你要怎么办
This is terrible, what are you going to do?
不知道  我的奶奶活着就是为了看我演戏
I don't know. This little, old lady lives for my career.
上回《我们的日子》不要我
When they dumped me off of Days of Our Lives
她差点难过到死掉
she almost died.
那样很不妙
That's not good.
快笑  别用那种表情  大家继续笑
No, smile! Not that face, smile! Everybody smile!
乔伊  你怎么不实话实说
Joey, why don't you just tell her what happened?
那又不能怪你
It's not your fault.
如果我们继续这样说话  会不会吓到她
If we keep talking this way, aren't we gonna freak her out soon?
很快  马上就到我出场了  那就是我
Soon, soon, I'm gonna be on soon. There I am!
不  山姆·沃特森
No! Sam Waterston!
不对  那是我
No-no-no, that-that's me, that's me.
不是  那是山姆·沃特森
No, it's Sam Waterston!
《罪与错》《摩羯宫一号》
Crimes and Misdemeanors, Capricorn One.
她听不懂"你好"  却知道《摩羯宫一号》
She doesn't know, "Hello." But she knows Capricorn One.
菲比
Phoebe!
我要那副耳环
I have to have those earrings,
电视剧一完我们就要出去了
we're going to leave as soon as the show is over.
可是我已经还你了啊
But I already gave them back to you!
你没有
No you didn't.
好  我已经没有还给你
All right, I already didn't give them back to you,
我就是这样说的啊
that's what I said.
另一只耳环在哪里
Where is that other earring?
菲比  不在这里
It's not here Pheebs, it's not here.
我昨晚有去钱德勒和乔伊那里
Ohh, I went to Joey and Chandler's last night!
好  记得要检查钱德勒的珠宝盒
Okay, make sure you check Chandler's jewelry box.
慢着  钱德勒有珠宝盒吗
Wait a minute. Chandler has a jewelry box?
好了  时间紧迫  你要我现在跟你解释吗
Okay, we have like ten minutes. Do you want me to get into that now?!
菲比
Hey Pheebs!
那个素食披萨  你吃得还习惯吗
How's that uh, vegetarian pizza working out for ya?
你和那些蔬菜还真够亲密的  是吧
You and those vegetables have a real thing going on, huh?
你干嘛怪里怪气的
Why are you being weird?
你喜不喜欢
Do you like it?
不喜欢  否则我就会问"你干嘛装可爱"
No, that would be, "Why are you being cute?"
好吧  我在练习打情骂俏
Okay, I'm working on my flirting.
原来如此  我没看出来
Ohh! I did not get that.
莫妮卡  你喜欢看《法律与秩序》吗
So uh Monica, do you, do you like the Law & Order?
喜欢  很好看
Yeah, it's good.
我今天发现到了新的你
See, I'm finding out all this stuff about you today,
比如说你爱看《法律与秩序》
like you like the Law & Order
你跟纽约及周边地区的所有男人打情骂俏
and that you flirted with every guy in the Tri-State area!
好  我来说个清楚
Okay, let me get this straight,
你可以打情骂俏  我却不行
it's okay for you to flirt, but not for me.
真高兴我们把话说清楚了
Oh, I'm so glad we cleared that up.
抱歉  但有些事  是男女有别的
Look, I'm sorry, but some things are different for men and for women.
继续  教我下什么叫男女有别
Go on, teach me something about men and women.
好吧  虽然我已经教过你很多了
Okay, I've already taught you so much already, but whatever.
你跟男人打情骂俏的时候
See when you flirt with a guy you think,
你觉得只是打情骂俏  没啥大不了的
"I'm just flirting, no big deal."
但对方会觉得
But the guy is thinking,
"终于  有人想跟我上床了"
"Finally! Somebody who wants to sleep with me!"
不可能
No way!
这是真的
It's true.
真可悲
Well that's pathetic!
这也是真的
Again true.
男人都这样吗
And this goes for all guys?
醒着的男人都这样
All guys that are awake.
等我们上床睡觉后
Then we go to sleep
世界另一边的男人起床
and then all the guys from the other end of the world
继续做一模一样的事
wake up and behave the exact same way.
又放广告了  我还是没跟她说
All right, it's another commercial; I still haven't told her!
乔伊  这是最后一段广告
Joey! This is like the last commercial.
你只剩十分钟了
You've got like  ten minutes left!
我知道  你要我怎么办
I know, I know! What am I going to do?
不许你跑路  留她在这里
No! You are not gonna run out and leave her here!
好啦
Yeah, all right.
乔伊
Joey!
乔伊马上回来
Uh, Joey is gonna be right back.
马上回来
Right back!
我们顺便来聊聊你吧
Meanwhile, let's-let's-let's talk about you.
你年纪大个子小
So, you're old and small.
找到没
Did you find it?
没找到耳环
The earring? No.
但在沙发底下找到了我的太阳眼镜
But look, I found my sunglasses under the couch!
我从去年夏天找到现在
I've been looking for these since like last summer.
那是我借给你的太阳眼镜
Okay, those are my sunglasses, you borrowed them from me.
好了  别激动  还你就是了
Okay, calm down, here they are.
菲比
Phoebe!
我们要怎么办
What are we going to do?!
我不知道
I don't know, I don't know.
我们只好老实跟莫妮卡说了
All right well, we're just gonna have to tell Monica, that's all.
老天  她一定会杀了我
Oh gosh, she's going to kill me.
我可以跟她说是我弄掉的
I suppose I could tell her it's just all my fault.
那就太好了
Ohh that'd be great!
莫妮卡  我有话要跟你说
Mon, can I talk to you for a sec?
好  什么事
Yeah, what is it?
我弄丢了你一只耳环
Umm, I lost one of your earrings.
对不起  我真的很抱歉
I'm sorry! I am so, so sorry!
好吧  都弄丢了还能怎样
All right well, I mean, what can you do? If you lost it you lost it.
我保证会赔你一副新的  我真的很愧疚
I will replace it, I promise. I feel so terrible.
亲爱的  没关系  你又不是故意的
All right, sweetie that's fine. You didn't do it on purpose.
当然不
No.
瞧你难过的  来
Look at you! Come here!
好点了没
Feel better?
有啊  你最棒了
Yeah! You're the best!
好了  等一等
Okay, wait a minute.
我不能这样
Wait a minute, I-I-I, I can't do this.
亲爱的  其实不是菲比弄丢的
Listen honey, this is, it's not Phoebe's fault.
她把你的耳环借我  我弄丢了
She lent me the earrings, and I lost it.
我真的很抱歉  亲爱的  我也好愧疚
I'm so sorry. Honey, I feel terrible too.
所以我才不借你东西
That is exactly why I do not lend you stuff!! Okay?!
先是我的首饰
I mean, first it's my jewelry!
然后又弄丢我的蓝色毛衣
And if it's not my jewelry, it's-it's my blue sweater!
还有我的太阳眼镜
And if it's not my sweater, it's my sunglasses!
你的太阳眼镜
Your sunglasses?!
-是的  -对哦
- Yes! - Oh, right!
披萨外送
Pizza!
我去  我去
Oh, mine! Mine! Mine!
要开始了
Okay, here goes.
准备见识下一流的打情骂俏
Prepare yourselves for some Class A flirting.
等等  我准备好了
Okay, hold on. Okay.
你犯不着这样
Honey, you have nothing to prove.
若你真的喜欢这个女孩
And if you really like this girl,
我不觉得你该打情骂俏
I don't thing flirting is the right thing to...
等着看就知道
You'll see. Okay.
她叫什么名字来着
Oh, what's-what's her name?
-凯特琳  -凯特琳
- Caitlin! - Caitlin!
这样吃下去也不是办法
Hey! Oh, we-we can't keep eating like this.
十二块五毛
It's uh, $12.50.
好的  那个
Okay, so,
做披萨是用烧木头的炉子吗
do you make the pizzas in one of those uh, wood-burning ovens?
不是  应该是煤气炉
No actually umm, I think that they're umm, gas.
煤气炉  哇
Gas? Wow!
真带劲
Intense.
如果盖勒家的人都这样打情骂俏的话
If this is the way all the Gellers flirt,
我们没问题了
we don't have a problem.
你知道煤气有味道吗
Hey uh, y'know that smell gas has?
-知道  -那是加进去的
- Yeah. - They put that in.
什么
What?!
煤气其实是无味的
The gas is odorless,
加上味道是为了让人
but they add the smell
在煤气泄漏时能闻出来
so you know when there's a leak.
好吧
Well okay!
很多气体都有味道
A lot of other gas smells...
救命哦
Oh the humanity.
甲烷有味道
Meth-methane smells...
不好意思  我真的得走了
Y'know what umm, actually I, I really, I should go.
我还没付钱呢
Oh but I-I-I haven't paid you yet!
没关系
Y'know what? That's okay,
你们点了那么多  这一个算我请的
you guys have ordered so many that this one is on me!
我是不是跟她说到了煤气
Was I talking to her about gas?
那根本就是主题
More so than anything else.
我觉得很有意思
I-I-I found it interesting.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
别担心
Look, no-no, hey, hey, don't worry about it!
九年之后  我和她就能在一起了
In nine years, she and I will be right there.
好了  我去清掉这些披萨盒
Okay, well, I'm gonna clear out some of these boxes.
-罗斯  -什么事
- Ross. - Yeah?
还有哪些气体会加味道
What else do they add smell too?
你好  我是瑞秋
Hey! Hey! Hi! Hey-hey-hey, I'm Rachel!
住楼上的  叫了一堆披萨的那家
From upstairs? The people with all the pizza?
披萨有问题吗
Oh, is there a problem?
不是  披萨很好吃
No. No. Every thing's--they're fine. Great pizza.
其实是我朋友罗斯的事
But it's uh, actually umm my friend Ross.
他只要打情骂俏就会紧张
He uh, just gets really nervous when he's flirting.
天啊  他是在打情骂俏吗
Oh my God! That was flirting?!
是的
Yeah.
我知道你的感觉  但我要告诉你
I know, I know, but uh just, I'm telling you, once,
一旦过了那个阶段
once you get past that part,
那个让你想死的阶段
that where it-it just feels like you wanna die,
你就会发现他是个大好人
he's-he's really a good person.
开口闭口都是煤气的那个人
The guy with the gas?!
他真的很体贴
Yeah. I'm-I'm telling you he's really sweet
而且风趣  还有一副好心肠
and he's really funny and he's just ugh, got a good heart.
而且我觉得他很喜欢你
And besides, I y'know, I think he really likes you.
真的吗
Really?!
我们七个人  却叫了十个披萨
Well y'know, we have 7 people and like 10 pizzas,
这还不够明显吗
what do you think?
乔伊不是在那里吗
I just, I thought Joey was there.
罗斯
Hey Ross?
我刚才在走廊遇到凯特琳
Umm, I just ran into Caitlin in the hallway and-and uh,
你打情骂俏的技巧  肯定比我想象中更高明
you must be getting better at this flirting stuff than I thought.
什么意思
What do you mean?
虽然我搞不懂
Well, I don't get it,
但她要我把电话号码转交给你
but she wanted me to give you her phone number.
她自己给你的
And she just gave you this?
是啊
Yeah!
瑞秋  谢了  但我不需要你帮忙
Rach, thanks but uh, I don't need you doing me any favors.
我没帮忙啊  是她觉得你可爱
I-I-I didn't! I didn't! She thought you were cute.
这点我倒是相信
Well that I can believe.
还在演吗
Hey! Is the show still on?
快要演完了
Almost over man.
快看  那是教皇吗
Look! Oh! Is that the Pope?!
我干嘛跟过去看
Why am I looking?
来了  我的好戏开演了
Oh, here I am, here's my big scene!
快退后
All right back off!
我有枪哦  用起来可不会手软
I gotta gun! I'm not afraid to use it!
乔伊
Oh Joey!
棒吧
That's right!
你起码也该换件衣服吧
You couldn't have at least changed your shirt.
我要一个装满十万美元的手提箱
Now, I wanna a suitcase filled with 100,000 dollars.
装满十万美元的小钞  若是我没拿到
Filled with $100,000 in small bills, and if I don't get it...
若是我没拿到
And if I don't get it,
我就毙了这只鸭子
I'm gonna shoot this duck!
不要啊
Oh no!
我要出去了
I'm comin' out!
-她会相信吗  -乔伊  太精彩了
- And she's supposed to buy this?! - Joey, bravo!
地面控制呼叫汤姆少校
Ground control to Major Tom!
倒计时开始
Commencing countdown...
引擎启动
engines...on!
这是下周的预告  下周的
That's uh, scenes from next week's show. Next week's!
我一定会看的
I am definitely gonna watch that!
这一对呢  看起来一样吗
What about these? These look the same?
当然了
Definitely!
是跟那对耳环比
Not as each other!
那就不一样了
Oh, then no.
准备好了没
You ready?
你真美  我是全世界最幸运的男人
You look amazing. I'm the luckiest man in the world.
你即将要更幸运了
Ohh, you're about to get a little luckier.
让我看看耳环
Let me see the earrings.
亲爱的  耳环
Oh, honey, the earrings...
好看极了  你男朋友真是品味一流
They look great! Does your boyfriend have the best taste or what?
我男朋友的品味真的很棒
My boyfriend really does have good taste!
多谢你帮我选耳环
Thanks for picking out the earrings man.